Welcome to MariusDesigner's tutorial video.
In this tutorial video, we will learn how to create a flower-shaped air bed.
First, please open the flat bed file, which can be downloaded in the description.
To create the air bed line, you need to draw the inner circle on the board.
Please select the inner circle tool, click on the board and drag the mouse to create the circle.
After drawing, press Ctrl-C and then Ctrl-V. The moving mouse can see the blueprint.
The moving mouse can see the blueprint.
At this time, press the mouse button to enter the number and the number of duplicates.
After setting up the number, duplicate and paste it again to line up the inner circle.
When the number of inner circles is not enough, please duplicate and paste an inner circle.
Adjust the position of the inner circle and copy and paste the inner circle to fill the entire panel.
To create a full-face panel, you need to use the outer layer function to create another layer.
To prevent the inner panel from deforming, freeze these panels.
Remove the face of the outer panel.
If you directly simulate it, the panel's surface effect is not obvious.
The point of moving the corner is to enlarge the outer panel.
There is enough material to complete the surface effect.
Increase the pressure to 50 to achieve the surface effect.
To see the simulation, you can see that the pattern and surface effect have already been created.
In order to make the circular part look tighter, you can set the inner circle to 50.
As the fold is created, the shape on the panel is also clearer.
Reduce the pressure to 50 to achieve a more detailed fold effect.
The struggle will stay the same.
Repeat the correct fold before even applying butter.
Increase the pressure to 50 to achieve a more precise fold effect.
It is important to achieve a smooth號ling effect.
Change the주 spending рабvat
Let's take a look at the creases and creases on the fabric
The creases on the fabric on the version will be very obvious, and the creases on the fabric will be less visible
The fabric is very soft and fluffy when used with a fabric with a very small creasing force on the corner line
The creases also form a gap due to the compression of the creases
Therefore, after changing the fabric, you can adjust the pressure again to get a more suitable effect
But not all silk is very soft, the shape of the creases is very hard, and the surface effect is not ideal
When the inner line has been sewed, keep changing the fabric to check the shape
It may cause the shape to be distorted
At this time, you can reset the arrangement of the version and re-model it to get a better creasing effect
See you in the next video, bye bye
Thank you for watching
If you liked the video, please subscribe to the channel and press the bell to receive notifications when I upload a new video
See you in the next video